labels	text	cls
B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	R.H. Saunders ( St. Lawrence River ) ( 968 MW )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O	; ' '' Anders Lindström '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O	Karl Ove Knausgård ( born 1968 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Atlantic City , New Jersey	False
O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O O	Her daughter from the second marriage was Marie d'Agoult ( 1805–1876 ) , who in turn gave birth to several children , among them—from her liaison to Franz Liszt –- Cosima Wagner ( 1837–1930 ) .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	St. Mary 's Catholic Church ( Sandusky , Ohio )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Shhh ... Do n't Tell ''	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Antonín Rýgr ( 1970–72 )	False
B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER	Dia Evtimova Catalina Castaño Dinah Pfizenmaier Tatjana Malek	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG	102.7 MHz Triple J – ABC	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	*20px Idaho State Highway 5	False
O B_LOC O O O O	'' Atelocentra '' Meyrick , 1884	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O O	' '' Antarctic prion '' '	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	James Franco ( M.F.A .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Civic Freedom Party	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	キイロキリガ — Xanthia togata '' ( Esper , 1788 )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	*August 8 – Craig Breslow	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	He has also won the Japan Senior Open twice .	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER O	His great-grandson is director Whit Stillman .	False
O O O B_ORG O O O	'' ' '' Chauliodus '' ' ''	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER	Janaki]] , S. P. Balasubrahmanyam	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	en:: ' '' Thornhill Islanders '' ' defeated Markham Waxers ''4-games-to-3 ''	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	Obituary of Juliette Peirce .	False
O O O B_LOC O	78 '' in Osnabrück .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Gian Girolamo Albani	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER O O O	`` Rhinestone Cowboy '' ( Larry Weiss ) - en:3:15	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	*Episode 9 - Michael Conlan	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Antawn Jamison ( 28 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	Chillicothe Paints ( 1993–2008 , joined the Prospect League )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Antoine Dadin de Hauteserre	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	1978 demo released on Off the Wall ( Special Edition ) '' ( 2001 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Carina Witthöft , 6–3 , 7–5	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC	File en:: CCStaClara.JPG|Through Santa Clara	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Eveno-Bytantaysky National District	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O	'' Euxoa centralis '' ( Staudinger , 1889 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Diocese of San Andrés Tuxtla	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Palisades , New York	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Rosephanye Powell ( born 1962 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Chum Ta Bong District	False
B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Epica – Consign to Oblivion ''	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Epirrhoe rivata '' ( Hübner , 1813 )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	** '' Justice League Elite '' en::	False
O O O O B_LOC O	It is found in Peru .	False
O B_LOC O O O O O O	** Ecuador en:: 7 % of the population	False
O O B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Translator of KCCV-FM , Overland Park , Kansas	False
O B_PER I_PER O	Mrs Brigitte Vallée .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lipiny , Ciechanów County	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Tatiana Volosozhar / Maxim Trankov	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Raymerville – Markville East , Ontario	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Robert Maxwell , 5th Lord Maxwell ( 1493–1546 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O O	Prince Rupert of the Rhine 15 August 1672 – 19 November 1682	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Železničná spoločnosť Slovensko	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC O O O	On February 6 , 1925 he retired from active duty and died in Santiago in 1938 .	False
O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	The 67 's finished in last place in the 2012–13 OHL season with just 16 wins .	False
O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	It was released as the first single from their 2004 album Everybody Loves a Happy Ending '' and is the first single that features both original members Roland Orzabal and Curt Smith since 1990 .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	Conservative]] Leader David Cameron )	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	Much of the story takes place in Flagstaff , Arizona , where Sgt .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG	'' Invisible Touch '' – Genesis	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	United States Senate Librarian	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Live at Sin-é ( Legacy Edition ) ''	False
O O B_LOC O O O O O B_LOC O O	' '' Calgary '' ' , ' '' Canada '' '	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O B_PER I_PER	*2001 – Hugh Hefner , Roastmaster Jimmy Kimmel	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Aigle Noir AC	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Hathaways Mountain Pines , California	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Peter T. King	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Charlie Clouser – Nine Inch Nails	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	Former collegiate church St Bartholomew , Liège	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Zlaté Moravce District	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Wilhelm Gustav Franz Herter	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Thomasville , Missouri	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Clement Poitrenaud , 14 .	False
B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC	Yahn | Yazdan Chah | Yegi | Yekkeh Derakht | Yosht | Yusefabad | Yush | Yushu	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	1982 Tour de France	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	John Denison-Pender , 1st Baron Pender	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Glyphipterix iometalla '' ( Meyrick , 1880 )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Zygaena cynarae '' ( Esper , 1789 )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	'' Super World of Sports '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Chananel ben Chushiel	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Bobby Rush ( D )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Legend of Chun Hyang ''	False
B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	BBC ( Test Match Special '' )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Bruce Beresford ( Non-Jew )	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG O O	It was also released along with Visual Studio 2005 , Microsoft SQL Server 2005 , and BizTalk 2006 .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Leonardo Rodríguez Solís	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O O O O O	She was born in Aldsworth , Gloucestershire , England on 10 January 1836 .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	** Kyoto National Museum ( early production cast )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of years in Brazil	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O	It is found in Mexico , Guatemala , Costa Rica , Panama , Colombia , Venezuela and Brazil .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O	' '' Michele Morosini '' ' ( 1308–1382 ) was ''doge '' from June 1382 until his death in October of the same year .	False
O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	20px Władysław I the Elbow-high	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O O O O O O O O	Misawa AB , Japan , 29 November 1965 – 15 May 1971	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Flatnose xenocongrid eel	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O	He resigned in March 1906 to run for West Hobart , but was unsuccessful .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lăpugiu de Jos	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Chinantec of Ozumacín	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	*October 4 – Drew Stubbs	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O	16th Troop Carrier Squadron en:: attached 14 November 1954 – 8 July 1955	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	File en:: Bdg fontannaPotop 2 10-2013.jpg|View from the foutain `` Deluge ''	False
O O O O B_PER O O O	It was described by Warren in 1892 .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Varghese Payyappilly Palakkappilly	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_PER O B_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O	It sold 184,000 in traditional album sales ( down 65 percent ) and was beaten to the top by Adele 's 25 '' , which debuted at number one with a record-breaking 3.38 million .	False
O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He was born in in Sundridge , Ontario .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG	Super League Greece en:: 1982–83	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG O	Guy Berryman ( Coldplay )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Jason Schwartzman , Isabelle Huppert , Dustin Hoffman	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Lena Springs '' '	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	He is a former England under-21 international .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O	Clement of Alexandria , ''Stromata '' 1.131.6 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Human Rights Commission of Malaysia	False
O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	The elevation is 3944 feet ( 1202 m ) above sea level .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Jean Frédéric Frenet	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	** '' Duchy of Naples '' ' – Gregory III ( 864–870 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Poland in the Eurovision Song Contest	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	'' Space Heater ( album ) ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Thompson International Speedway – Thompson , Connecticut	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O	Recorded at Alberts Studio , London .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	West Herzegovina Canton	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Ili Kazakh Autonomous Prefecture	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	**London en:: Thames & Hudson .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	Takht Sri Hazur Sahib , Nanded	False
O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	lifebelt]]s that survived the sinking is on display at the Imperial War Museum North in Manchester	False
O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O	His father was Abd Manaf ibn Qusai .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O B_LOC	Borg El Arab Stadium , Alexandria , Egypt	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` A Different Corner ''	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG	1283 en:: The Yuan Dynasty claim possession of the Penghu Islands	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Alain Delon , Richard Conte , Carla Gravina	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Zadie Smith '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Glencoe , KwaZulu-Natal	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Polystichum acrostichoides '' ( Michx .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` You 're the Voice ''	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	A few months later two planes , one of them named ''Atlântico '' , were sent by ship to Montevideo and flown to Buenos Aires .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	New York State Route 5	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Des pères , des hommes et des frères	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC O	Before 1945 the area was part of Germany .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	5000-meter run – en:14:15.61 ( 2015 )	False
B_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Sridevi , Sanjay Dutt , Rahul Roy	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Miranda Martino as the Singer	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	Communist Party of Nigeria ( CPN )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_LOC I_LOC	** '' Chaetodon falcula '' , Blackwedged butterflyfish	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	The first settlers arrived in the early 19th century , and were largely Quakers , Mennonites and United Empire Loyalists who had left the United States .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Republic of Ezo ( 1868–1869 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Hul , Nové Zámky District	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG B_LOC O B_LOC	Estadio Tiburcio Carías Andino Tegucigalpa , Honduras	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Bokówka , Podlaskie Voivodeship	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Robert A. Borski , Jr .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Perry Township , Fayette County , Ohio	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	'' Tsardom of Russia '' ' – Feodor III ( 1676–1682 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	St George 's , University of London ( SGUL )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Wales national football team	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	*wisent ( Bison bonasus '' )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Warrandyte South , Victoria	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Prochoreutis stellaris '' ( Zeller , 1847 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG O	UEFA Cup winner 1981 .	False
O O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O	In 1926 he was promoted to the rank of Marshal of Italy .	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O B_ORG B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	Her grandson Stanley Eric Francis Booth-Clibborn became the Anglican Bishop of Manchester .	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	It will serve the suburb of Murrumba Downs in the Moreton Bay Region .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Lawrence of Rome	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	The Larry Sanders Show ''	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG O	Coming on twice as a substitute , he was selected to start in the semi-final loss to Brazil .	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER	'' September 7 '' – Little Shop	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	It is in Division No. 6 , in the Bay of Exploits .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O	Alexander of Hales , ( died 1245 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Louis Eppolito and Stephen Caracappa	False
O O O B_LOC	''Slavonija '' en:: Slavonia	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O	John Steven Sutherland ( born 11 March 1983 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	K. S. Rangasamy College of Technology	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	St. Mary 's College , Kegalle	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	*Liam references Lucky Charms .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O B_LOC	Classic Gold Marcher , Wrexham and Chester	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O	DRS 1 - 101.5 MHz ( 60 kW )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Marvin Dunnette , University of Minnesota	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Get off the Stage	False
O B_ORG O O B_PER	'' Şımarık '' – Tarkan	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O	GMA Network was also reportedly planning to bid but backed out ; it however denied that they offered a bid .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	' '' Slobodan Živojinović '' ' 7–6 6–3 6–4	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	K. Stade Leuven ( 1903—2002 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Patrick Ryan ( Irish priest )	False
O O O B_ORG O B_LOC O B_LOC	Image en:: V02p108001 Esnoga , Amsterdam , Netherlands	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Graphium endochus '' ( Boisduval , 1836 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Circuit rider ( Technology )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Tachibana no Naramaro	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Rajiv Gandhi International Cricket Stadium	False
O B_LOC O B_LOC	- Alanya in Turkey	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O	He was the manager of Árabe Unido in Panama .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Central , Tennessee ( CDP )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	*20px Indiana State Road 18	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O O	It is known from Iran and Turkmenistan ( Kopet Dag ) .	False
O B_PER O O O	1–0 Ewerthon ( 28 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	2014 Women 's Futsal World Tournament	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Guatemalan pygmy owl	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	LAC+USC Medical Center	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Marion Township , Hardin County , Ohio	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Maurie Keane '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Northern rough-winged swallow	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Caroline Hedwall ( T12 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Winnie the Pooh ( franchise )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Aubrey J. O'Brien	False
O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O	Including the work of artists such as en:: Edward Burne-Jones , Ford Madox Brown , John Everett Millais , Dante Gabriel Rossetti , William Holman Hunt , Arthur Hughes , Frederick Sandys , Simeon Solomon .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Weverton , Maryland	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Cleinias of Tarentum	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O B_ORG I_ORG O	The eastward pressure to expand was also created by the inability to move westward , inhibited by the formidable presence of the enormous Flushing Chinatown ( 法拉盛華埠 ) centered on Main Street .	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Arnold Schwarzenegger , Linda Hamilton , Robert Patrick , Edward Furlong	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of national libraries	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Frederick Banbury , 1st Baron Banbury of Southam	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` Who Loves You ? ''	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O	''Oberst '' Kurt Freiherr von Liebenstein , 21 December 1942 – 1 January 1943 ( acting leader )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	** Southern Maryland Blue Crabs	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Casey Janssen ( 6 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of famous Puerto Ricans	False
O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	`` Simply Meant to Be '' ( with Jennifer Warnes )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Rhodophthitus tricoloraria '' ( Mabille , 1890 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Leo II of Galicia	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	William Morrow and Company	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	Wusi Road Subdistrict ( )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Jane Levy , Dylan Minnette , Stephen Lang	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	It is found in Costa Rica .	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O	In 1841 the population of Norbury and Roston was 510 , in 1895 there were 414 inhabitants .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	''Written by William Barton ''	False
B_LOC O O O	Lantenay ( 01206 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	John Reeves ( judge )	False
B_LOC I_LOC O O O	La Clotte ( 17113 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Edwin S. Johnson ( D )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O	Funahashi Seiichi ( December 25 , 1904 – January 13 , 1976 )	False
O O O O B_LOC O	It is known from Chile .	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O	AFL]] ( Australian rules )	False
O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O	Among many artists who recorded this song were Al Jolson and Billy Murray .	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	** '' Duchy of Aquitaine '' ' – William V ( 995–1030 )	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O	' '' West African lion '' ' ( ''P .	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	'' The Room '' ( Chris Waters , Tom Shapiro ) – en:3:40	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O	Munsee-Delaware Nation Indian Reserve No. 1 , part of the above	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O B_LOC O O O O B_LOC O	It lies north-west of Kowalewo Pomorskie , north-west of Golub-Dobrzyń , and north-east of Toruń .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O B_ORG	Bahawalpur Zoo , Bahawalpur , Punjab	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Friedrich Gilly ( 1772–1800 )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O	**** Longtail stingray ( ''D .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of Orchidaceae genera	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Clarkston railway station	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O	Rimyongsu Sports Club ( Sariwon )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Len Braund ( 1901–1907 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Martin Luther King , Jr .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Verner Thomé ( 1878–1953 )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	1944 Presentation Brothers College	False
B_PER I_PER O B_LOC	Jörgen Olsson , Sweden	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	''Also see en:: Hot 100 No. 1 Hits of 1979 ''	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He died on March 19 , 1979 in Oakland , California .	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	'' Too Many Hands '' ( Randy Meisner , Don Felder ) – en:4:43	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Masonic Temple Building ( Maywood , Illinois )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Shake ( company )	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O	He ultimately returned to the Boston Globe '' , where he had been working immediately before the ''Tribune '' had hired him .	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Psolos fuligo fuligo '' — '' 'Coon '' '	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Sid Wilson ( 0 )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Jan Niklas , Désirée Nosbusch	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	** Trail of Tears , 1830–1838	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	United States Department of Labor	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	Jared Dudley , Emeka Okafor , Jason Richardson ( 9 )	False
O O O O O O O O B_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG O O O B_PER O B_ORG O O	The first 3 songs as PopCrush 97.1 were Pitbull / Christina Aguilera 's Feel This Moment '' , Justin Timberlake 's Mirrors '' , and Rihanna 's Umbrella '' .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Tomáš Šmíd '' ( Third Round )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Chip Robinson ( 1986 )	False
O O O B_ORG O O O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	** ' '' Nanhai '' ' – Liu Yin , King of Nanhai ( 907–911 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Siege of Naples ( 542–43 )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG O	Clarence Tommerson , NFL player	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Naco-Mammoth Kill Site	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Communes of the Somme department	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Magnificent snake eel	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Francisco Menéndez Márquez	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Beecher , Michigan – $ 13,484	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	After a large and well attended funeral , he was interred in Green Lawn Cemetery .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of Indonesian birds en:: non-passerines	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Stade du 28 Septembre , Conakry	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Gujranwala '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Musa Haji Ismail Galal	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	The song is included in the album Yanni Voces '' .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	K. M. Seethi	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	East Chicago , Indiana	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Somerset ( town ) , Wisconsin	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Mika Häkkinen '' '	False
B_ORG B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	WTUA St. Stephen , South Carolina	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Kolkata '' '	False
B_ORG O O O O O B_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_LOC O	Taebong has been overthrown , and Goryeo established in the Korean peninsula , when Wang Kon ascends the throne at Cheorwon .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Sergey Shoygu ( 2012 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Tatem Elementary School , Collingswood , NJ	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Flick of the Switch ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	O. L. Owen ( 1898 )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	1911 Yeon Building , Portland , Oregon	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` O Come All Ye Faithful ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Conejo Valley Unified School District	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Dick 's Sporting Goods ( 80,000 ft² )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Acianthera rostellata '' ( Barb.Rodr .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Calhoun City , Mississippi	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Rockhead ( fish )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Cedar Lawn Cemetery , Paterson , New Jersey	False
O O O O B_PER O O O	It was described by Breuning in 1939 .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Pontianak ( folklore )	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC	Myrtle Beach , United States	False
O O B_LOC O	Tremoschna en:: Třemošná B,60	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	How to Save a Life ''	False
B_ORG O B_LOC O O O	Parken , Copenhagen ( H )	False
B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Tenerife , Canary Islands , Spain	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Sui Wenjing / Han Cong	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Now under control of 482nd Fighter Wing ( Air Force Reserve Command ) and Detachment 1 , 125th Fighter Wing ( Florida Air National Guard )	False
O O O O B_LOC O O O	אֶת חֶבְרוֹן וְאֶת מִגְרָשֶׁהָ Hebron and its periphery	False
B_LOC O O O O	Voznesensk ( Вознесенський район )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Chimneys of Poolbeg Generating Station	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	This Hour Has 22 Minutes '' cast	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Lucas Arnold Ker '' ' ' '' Sebastián Prieto '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Bernhard Warkentin Homestead	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O	She currently lives in Los Angeles , California .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Princess Clémentine of Belgium	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Andrex ( actor )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Martin Sheen - The West Wing ''	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` U Got It Bad ''	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Ruanda-Urundi '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	Bright Size Life '' – Pat Metheny	False
B_PER O O O	Vulcana ( 1875–1946 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Society of the Friends of Truth	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Indian flying frog	False
B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC	Knightville Dam – Westfield River	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Aborigines ' Protection Society	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Memphrémagog Regional County Municipality	False
O O B_ORG O O	' '' CBS '' '	False
O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	*1951 - 1980 Sir William Rede Hawthorne	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Herbert Brownell , Jr .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	George Caspar Adams ( 1863–1900 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Franz von Papen	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O	Lee Trevino won the most tournaments , six .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	East Brunswick , New Jersey .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Head of government en:: Prime Minister of Andorra	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	Recorded by Fats Waller .	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG O O B_LOC O	Previously , he was head coach at Alcorn State University and an assistant coach at Tulane , Delta State , LSU , Florida , Marshall , Southern Miss , Ole Miss , Michigan , and Memphis .	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC O O O O O B_LOC O	Five years later , in 1939 , Edern was abolished and incorporated into Nefyn .	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER	' '' Second en:: ' '' Kaho Onodera	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Leopold , Grand Duke of Baden	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC	Oriole Park at Camden Yards in Baltimore , Maryland , United States	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Massachusetts Route 3A	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Fulvio Ballabio ( 1988 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Meigs Township , Muskingum County , Ohio	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O	He was born in Glasgow , Scotland .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Gmina Tarnów Opolski	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	Hernán Cortés was his relative , whom he accompanied to Mexico ( New Spain ) in 1526 .	False
O O B_ORG O O O	File en:: Tiananmen ( 天安门 )	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Episode en:: `` It 's My Party and I 'll Lie if I Want To ''	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O	He is a son of Alan Lennox-Boyd , 1st Viscount Boyd of Merton .	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He died on August 25 , 1992 in Boca Raton , Florida .	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Nothin ' But Trouble '' ( 1988 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lynn Township , McLeod County , Minnesota	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He resides in Monmouth Junction , New Jersey .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	FM Radio Gods	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O O O	'' Aztec Empire '' ' – Tenoch , Great Speaker ( 1325–1376 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	J. R. R. Tolkien	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' Speed Up '' '	False
O O O O O O B_LOC B_LOC	*36th on 10 November 2005 , Calgary CAN	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_LOC O B_LOC O	He graduated in 1970 with a Doctor of veterinary medicine degree from the Ontario Veterinary College , University of Guelph in nearby Guelph , Ontario .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Paul Tang ( 2007 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Melissa Hayden ( 1945–1947 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Waveguide ( optics )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Las Cruces , New Mexico	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O	Radu Albot / Artem Sitak , 6–4 , 7–6 ( 7–3 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER	`` by Arthur Byron Cover	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O	'' Aletia infrargyrea ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	The Dirty Dozen Brass Band	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Márcio Rogério de Andrade	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Marshal ( Japan )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Cephissus ( Athenian plain )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Francis Wayland Parker	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O	'' Valsa ceratosperma ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	St Ann 's College	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` I Promise to Wait My Love ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC O	National Nursing Week ( United States )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	The Outdoor Room	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Hell en:: The Sequel ''	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	He was educated at the Community High School , Tehran and then Carlisle Technical College .	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_LOC O O O O	In 1960 , he joined the U.S. Army , being stationed in Germany for three years .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Beijing No.8 High School	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O	Ashdot Ya'akov Meuhad ( 1953 ) , from Ashdot Ya'akov ( 1924 , 1933 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lacs de Conzieu	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Monmouth , Illinois – $ 15,839	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Eastern Anatolia Region	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He died in July of 1969 in Williamsport , Pennsylvania .	False
O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG	''Review en:: Something Better to Come '' at Slant Magazine	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Returning to Norfolk , Virginia , 1 April 1946 , ''Calamares '' was decommissioned at Baltimore , Maryland , 25 April 1946 , and returned to the War Shipping Administration .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Platon ( Kulbusch )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Southampton F.C .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Chuuk flying fox	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	John Holles , 2nd Earl of Clare	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O	The Churches Conservation Trust now cares for the building .	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O O B_LOC I_LOC O	They originate from South Asia , Europe , Middle East , and East Africa .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Growing Up ( The T.G.I.S. Primetime )	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O	Following its sale by the New Zealand Railways Corporation in the 1990s , the building was turned into student accommodation by Auckland University and since 2008 has been occupied by private apartments .	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' With Chet Baker '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Çıraqlı , Lachin	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O	He is from Andhra Pradesh in South India .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O	53d Wing ( 53 WG )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	Oda Station ( Shimane ) ( 小田駅 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Tales from Turnpike House ''	False
B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC	Aboudeïa – Salamat Region	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Gibaeksan ( South Gyeongsang )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Rufus Choate ( W-MA )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Tony Albright '' '	False
B_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Live - `` Run to the Water ''	False
B_PER I_PER O O	Kunio Maekawa , architect	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	'' Kingdom of Scotland '' ' – William the Lion ( 1165–1214 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER	2008 en:: Janusz Morgenstern	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O	'' Platanthera bifolia ''	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	He spent much of his career with Swindon Town , for whom he played in the Premier League .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O	The Eastwood Westminster constituency was created in 1983 , and the Eastwood Holyrood constituency , with the same boundaries , in 1999 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	UEFA Women 's Euro 2013	False
O B_LOC O O	'' Toulouse '' '	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Rupert Hamer , LL.M. , MLC	False
B_PER O O O	Ka-Zar '' vol .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Masters of Darts ( 1 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Time Stays , We Go ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Listed buildings in Crawley	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Michel-Ange Duquesne de Menneville ( 1752–1755 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Poříčí nad Sázavou	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Celaenorrhinus homeyeri '' ( Plötz , 1880 )	False
B_PER B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	J. J. Johnson and Kai Winding	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER	Francisco del Rosario Sánchez , Juan Pablo Duarte and Matías Ramón Mella	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Rupert Young as Sir William Herbert , Lord Pembroke	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Black-bellied plover , ''Pluvialis squatarola ''	False
O O O B_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O	He is a goalkeeper for Lech Poznań .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Johannes V. Jensen	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Sean Paul Lockhart	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Montreal West , Quebec	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Văn Lãng District	False
O O O O O O B_ORG O	67 competitors were selected by the DLV .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Kalbar , Queensland	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Bobby 's Burger Palace	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Beulah Bondi ( 1888–1981 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Pelican Rapids , Minnesota – $ 13,699	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	This was published by the American Mathematical Society as ISSN 0038-5573 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Trilofo , Arcadia	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Melissa , Texas	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	''The Times '' ( Chicago ) , went defunct in 2005	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Laurence Helsby , Baron Helsby	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Ronaldinho Gaucho 's Team	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Rüppell 's robin-chat	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Thomas 's pine vole	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Tennessee in the Civil War	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Minarete Brass '' ( 2010 )	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	*2008 – `` All Summer Long '' – Kid Rock	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Hamdan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	It 's No Good	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC	North Fork Flathead - Canada , United States	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	DCLXVI en:: To Ride Shoot Straight and Speak the Truth ''	False
B_ORG O O O O	McCoy '' ( 1975-1976 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	The Price Is Right ( Philippine game show ) ''	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER O O O	*** '' Northern March '' ' – Lothair ( 983–1003 )	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Kentucky '' '	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	He claimed to be son of Khalilullah II .	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Dialectica imperialella '' ( Zeller , 1847 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Royal Australian Corps of Transport - The Princess Royal	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Johor Bahru City Square	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O	It is known from Kenya and Uganda .	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O	*9378 - Apamea burgessi ''	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Shooting guard / Small forward	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	Mount Marty College ( Yankton , South Dakota )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Three 's a Crowd	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' Persiaran APEC '' '	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Theretra jugurtha '' ( Boisduval , 1875 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O	Harvard Business School Press ( 2013 ) Managing Up en:: Expert Solutions to Everyday Challenges	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Marysville , Pennsylvania	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	St. Mary 's Church , South Stoneham	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O	He was a son of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart .	False
O O O B_LOC O	He hailed from Søgne .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Njego Pesa ( 1983–87 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Marco Melandri '' '	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG	Sun Quan en:: Nabatame Hitomi	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	David Clarke ( Paralympic footballer )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Comanche , Oklahoma	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Bova , Calabria	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lamb 's Conduit Field	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Doug McClure , Keith Barron	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER I_PER	Howard W. Hunter , Boyd K. Packer , Marvin J. Ashton , L. Tom Perry , David B. Haight , James E. Faust , Neal A. Maxwell , Russell M. Nelson , Dallin H. Oaks , M. Russell Ballard , Joseph B. Wirthlin , Richard G. Scott	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` I 'll Walk ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Silver Slipper , Las Vegas , Nevada	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Top Chef en:: Just Desserts ''	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` Wake Up Brother ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Pemba green pigeon	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	The ' '' 1994 Big Ten Conference Baseball Tournament '' ' was held at C. O. Brown Stadium in Battle Creek , Michigan from May 15 through 19 .	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O	' '' Robert B. Mautz '' '	False
O B_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	`` Carnival '' – Natalie Merchant	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Sharif Fati Ali Al Mishad	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Prince Talal bin Muhammad	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	2000 - Servants of Darkness ''	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Anne McLellan ( 1994-1997 )	False
O O O B_ORG O	The demand is $ .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Thomas Morgan ( MP died 1565 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Giancarlo Fisichella '' '	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O	He was Mayor of Exeter July 1414 to October 1415 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Brays Oaks , Houston	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O	He became a journalist for The Nashville American '' , serving as a correspondent from 1885 to 1892 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC O O O	Evans Bay is nearby .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	** Basilica of San Isidoro , León , Spain consecrated .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O	Sir Gilbert Heathcote , 3rd Baronet ( died 1785 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Lee Maye , LF ( 1965-1966 )	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	' '' Venue en:: ' '' Daegu Civic Stadium , Daegu	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Policarpo Cacherano d'Osasco	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O	Parliamentary elections on 22 September 2002 en:: 44.1 % of the primary vote	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Elachista quadripunctella '' ( Hübner , 1825 )	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	It is found in Cameroon and São Tomé and Príncipe .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Rupert Keegan took the B.A.R.C .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Miranda Cosgrove ( 1993- )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	' '' Mark Knowles '' ' / ' '' Daniel Nestor '' ' defeated Roger Federer / Max Mirnyi 6–4 , 6–4	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Uluçınar , İmamoğlu	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	José Luis de Arrese	False
O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	''65 Damien Woody G ( IR ) 7px	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	John Pratt , 1st Marquess Camden	False
O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	'' Jackie Evancho '' ' ( born 2000 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	NALSAR University of Law , Hyderabad	False
B_LOC O B_LOC O B_ORG	Toronto , Ontario - CITY	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` Livin ' on Borrowed Time ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	José Luis Reséndez	False
O B_ORG O O O O O O O	Broadcaster RAI chose the song and performer internally .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Mystery Science Theater 3000 ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant en:: 2,300	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Byzantium under the Macedonians	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Johan Caspar von Cicignon	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	North Vacherie , Louisiana	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG O O O B_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	1 en:: `` No News '' , `` Come Cryin ' to Me '' , `` Amazed '' , `` Smile '' , `` What About Now '' , `` Tell Her '' , `` I 'm Already There '' , `` My Front Porch Looking In '' , and `` Mr. Mom '' .	False
B_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG O	Shakira – `` Ojos Así ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	North Woodbridge , California	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Simone Terenzani ( 0,0,1,0,0,1,1,0 ) - 38 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	List of counties in Missouri	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	The Threshold of a Persona	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Grapholita funebrana '' Treitschke , 1835	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Rube Ellis ( 1911 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	*1986 en:: Herbert W. Franke , ''Endzeit ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Miranda de Azán	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O O	' '' Bukit Kepong '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Volcanoes National Park , Rwanda	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Terry George ( entrepreneur )	False
O O B_LOC O B_LOC O	Based in Lille and Versailles .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O	The John Tracy Clinic , named after her son , was the result .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	*The Bennington Battle Monument in Bennington , Vermont , 1889 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Westwood College – Dallas , Texas	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Anabelle Langlois / Patrice Archetto	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Part of the state-owned Main Line of Public Works	False
B_ORG B_LOC O O O O	Madiran Tannat ( 4–12 yrs )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O	Mia Wasikowska as Alice Kingsleigh .	False
B_PER I_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Alexandru Popovici ( 2001 Seongnam Ilhwa Chunma )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	' '' If You Ai n't Got a Weapon ... ''	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG O	It consists of the Bundesautobahn 3 , the Bundesautobahn 4 and the Bundesautobahn 1 .	False
O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O B_PER I_PER O	There have been five winners to date en:: Leanne Mitchell , Andrea Begley , Jermain Jackman , Stevie McCrorie and Kevin Simm .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Francesco Soto de Langa ( 1534–1619 )	False
O O O B_ORG O O O	' '' 14 Porsche '' ' ''	False
O O O O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O B_ORG O B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He subsequently worked for ABC affiliate WUTR in Utica , New York , CBS affiliate WTVH in Syracuse , New York , and NBC affiliate WCNC-TV in Charlotte , North Carolina .	False
O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	There were two main branches of the family , one in Dutton and the other in Sutton Weaver .	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	'' ' '' After the Love Has Gone '' Earth , Wind & Fire '' '	False
B_PER O O O	Decius ( 249-251 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O	Seán Óg Ó hAilpín en:: 3 ( 2003 , 2004 , 2005 )	False
O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O	*Has made several trips to the Middle East , visiting troops in Iraq and Afghanistan , as well as visiting Kyrgyzstan , Afghanistan , Kuwait , Bahrain , Saudi Arabia , the United Arab Emirates and Qatar .	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	'' Last Date '' ( Floyd Cramer ) – en:2:16	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Giovanni Battista Buonamente	False
B_ORG O O O O	Tazmania '' ( 2006 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Marcello Trotta ' ''	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	2369 Shickshinny , Pennsylvania $ 14,880	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Patagonian yellow finch	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' President 's Cup '' '	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	*Mr. Grimby - Richard Dumont	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	'' Tokimeki Memorial en:: Forever With You ''	False
O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O O B_LOC I_LOC	*The consisted of Centre , Clearfield , Lycoming , McKean , Northumberland , Potter , and Tioga Counties	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Arnaud Boetsch '' ( Second round ) ''	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Lornna Soto '' '	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG O	It premiered on 27 June 2010 on YouTube .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Wesley Pritchard ( 1996– ) 36	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Damon Stoudamire ( 3,018 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Călineasa River ( Someșul Cald )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O	Camille Paglia compares the resulting image to William Blake 's `` engravings of solipsistically contorted figures '' .	False
O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Assemblyman Peter J. Barnes III ( D )	False
O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	In 1854 he was appointed to a seat on the Legislative Council of Nova Scotia , upon the recommendation of William Young .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O B_LOC	Twickenham Stadium , London , England	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O O O O O	File en:: Southern Italy and Sicily on the 1849 map .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Petersburg , Virginia	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	His descendants include Vincenzo Viviani , a disciple and biographer of Galileo Galilei .	False
O O O O O O B_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O B_PER I_PER O	This was continued by his sons Edgar , Alexander I and in particular David I .	False
O O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O	He was Sworn in as a Member of the Queen 's Privy Council for Canada on 4 January 2011 .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	John Henry Crichton , Viscount Crichton	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O	She was the youngest-ever female Member of Parliament .	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	The song was recorded at Grouse Lodge , under the supervision of producer Jacknife Lee .	False
B_LOC O O O	Krapanj , population 170	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER I_PER	Ronald J. Garan , Jr . Michael E. Fossum	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	San Pedro y San Pablo Asistencia	False
B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O O	Red knot , ''Calidris canutus '' ( A )	False
B_LOC I_LOC O O	La Seyne-sur-Mer – 57,553	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	border ' '' Séamus Harnedy	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O	** Western gorilla ( ''G .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Lyraka Volume 1 ( 2010 ) ''	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Brunei '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Hälsingland Rune Inscription 21	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Joe Abercrombie , author ;	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Judge Reinhold , Fred Savage	False
B_LOC I_LOC O B_PER	Melaleuca delta '' Craven	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	The Beatles ' influence on popular culture	False
O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	His death was profiled in an episode of Unsolved Mysteries '' .	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Agrochola lota '' ( Clerck , 1759 )	False
O O O O O O O O B_ORG O B_LOC O O	Highest total against en:: 224 / 7 by Somerset at Taunton , 2015	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Mordellistena pseudoparvula '' Ermisch , 1956	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	All Saints Cathedral , Halifax	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Beginning of Karoo Ice Age .	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O	It is housed in the Musée du Louvre of Paris .	False
B_ORG I_ORG B_PER I_PER I_PER	Lotte Jonathans Paulien van Dooremalen	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Serra da Estrela Subregion	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	**09621 Amberg ( Oberpfalz )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	East Central Independent School District	False
O O O B_LOC O	en:: en:: en:: B. ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	The Jacksons ( TV series )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Reagan County , Texas	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	E. H. Shepard	False
O B_PER I_PER O O O	en:: Ashleigh Brewer ( 2014– )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Nowinki , Wołomin County	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Lyrics en:: Duncan Fallowell ) – en:3:30 / en:5:41	False
O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	*Lifetime Achievement - Arthur M. Schlesinger , Jr .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Hans Karl von Diebitsch	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Crombrugghia distans '' ( Zeller , 1847 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Rob Fusari – composer , producer	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	William O'Connor '' ( First round )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Albert Pujols [2] ( 2006 , 2010 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Mark Jones en:: ( 1991-1999 , 2006 )	False
B_LOC O O B_LOC O	Lugdunum ( modern Lyon )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Pioneer Square , Seattle	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Joe Shirley , Jr .	False
O O O O O B_ORG O O O O	The family eventually settled in Egypt in February 1944 .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	'' Pumped Up Kicks '' – Foster the People	False
O O B_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	' '' Tanzania '' ' - Jakaya Kikwete ( 1995-2006 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Brian Dillons GAA	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Ridley Scott / Hans Zimmer	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	Slavko Marić – Hajduk Beograd ( 2001–2006 ) , Mladost Lučani ( 2006–2008 ) , Borac Čačak ( 2008–2011 ) , Sloboda Užice ( 2011–2012 ) , Radnički Kragujevac ( 2012-2014 ) , ' '' FK Jagodina '' ' ( 2015–present )	False
O O O O B_PER O O O	It was described by Breuning in 1982 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Shipley , West Yorkshire	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Jefferson Davis ! ! 2 ! !	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC O O	They wed on 28 April 2007 in their Malibu home .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	Native North American Child en:: An Odyssey ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Redlich–Kwong equation of state	False
B_PER I_PER O B_ORG O O	Yu Darvish ( TEX ) en::	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O	'' Samurai 7 ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Dev ( actor )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Party of Action ( POA )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Princess Adélaïde of Orléans	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Children 's Day Festival	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Hedley , Texas	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Final Fantasy concerts	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Quta Qutani ( Bolivia )	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' 20px 99 Villeray '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	A Few Days with Me ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Crick , Northamptonshire	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	List of Serbian monarchs	False
B_PER I_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG O	R. Kelly – `` Satisfy You ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Turkish films of 2010	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Nemapogon ruricolella '' ( Stainton , 1859 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Latter Day Church of Christ	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	' '' DLCX '' ' - Waste Management , Inc .	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O	the `` Twelve Steps '' at the beginning of Chapter 5 `` How It Works ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC O O O O B_LOC I_LOC	Boundary Ranges , just S of Iskut River	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	'' Volumes 3 & 4 '' ( 1998 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Cauchy 's theorem ( geometry )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Eaton High School ( grades 9-12 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Prince Michael of Prussia ( 1940–2014 )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Anastasia Martiusheva / Alexei Rogonov	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	C.D. Atlético Junior	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Stick ( unit )	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC	Bridgwater Town , promoted as runners-up in Western League	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O	929th Troop Carrier Group en:: 11 February 1963 – 1 January 1964	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O O O	`` The Heart Wo n't Lie '' ( Kim Carnes , Donna Weiss ) - en:3:22	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Exeter Cathedral 1929 - 1937	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O O	''Crockett '' was laid down by the Tacoma Boatbuilding Company , Tacoma , Washington , and commissioned 24 June 1967 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Morrisania , Bronx	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O O	Governorate General of Brazil ( 1549-1572 / 1578-1607 / 1613-1621 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG	Football League Two third-place promotion en:: 2005–06	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	International Swimming Federation ( FINA )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Ethnic stereotypes in comics	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Chestnut-capped brush finch	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Spain '' '	False
O O O O O B_LOC O	en:09:00 PM ( VIA en:: Alagankulam )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	Air Command and Staff College , Seminar Program	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O	'' Eilema depressa '' ( Esper , 1787 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	North Carolina General Assembly of 2003–04	False
O B_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG	'' Robopit '' - Kokopeli Digital Studios / Altron	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Dominic Mafham as Robin Douglas-Home	False
O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	She was purposely sunk near Les Bergeronnes , Quebec in November 1960 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC	Vasil Levski National Military University , Veliko Tarnovo	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Smokey Robinson handled much of the production .	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	Member of Finnish Academy of Sciences , 2002–	False
B_PER I_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG O	Michael Jackson – `` Earth Song ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	National Union of Students ( Canada ) ( disbanded )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Patti McLeod276 ( 37.8 % )	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O	The resulting album , Last Fair Deal Gone Down '' was released in May 2001 .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O B_LOC O	43 - Nutpimon Natthayalak , ( Krabi )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Papilio alexanor '' Esper , 1800	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Thief River Falls , Minnesota	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Persona 2 en:: Innocent Sin	False
B_LOC I_LOC B_LOC	Rhododendron subg. Rhododendron	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Aleksander Barkov , Jr .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER O O O	`` Express Yourself '' , Madonna ( 1989 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Tony Parker ( 24 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Pierre Du Moulin	False
B_ORG O B_LOC O	Thalhimers ( Richmond )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Phil Gramm ( R-TX )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O	John Isner 7–6 ( 4 ) , 5–7 ( 5 ) , 7–5 , 6–4	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O	'' Eupithecia refertissima ''	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	He is part of the Czech Republic men 's national volleyball team .	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	800BC ( in The Odyssey '' )	False
B_LOC O O O O O	Dakaongo ( 1 245 inhabitants )	False
B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Center Township , Atchison County , Kansas	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	' '' Turkish Super Cup '' ' ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Metadata Object Description Schema	False
O O O O O O O O B_LOC O O O	Events from the year ' '' 1866 in Scotland '' ' .	False
O O O O O B_LOC O O O B_LOC O	It lies approximately south-east of Sicienko and north-west of Bydgoszcz .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Ted Freyer ( 52 )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O	He joined Ayr United in August 1999 , and remained with them until August 2000 .	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' Perth Thunder '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Maria Adams ( disambiguation )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Johann Ludwig Krebs	False
B_PER I_PER O B_LOC O	Constantine Dragaš ( Dragaš )	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Ami Koshimizu and Mamiko Noto	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Gérald V d'Armagnac	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Banyan ( clothing )	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O	He migrated to Mexico City in 1986 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Basilica della Santa Casa	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Full Circle '' ( 2004 )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	'' Col des Ares ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	Barry Mackay '' ( Quarterfinalist ) ''	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	Michael Bolton covered the song on his 1992 album Timeless en:: The Classics '' .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Christopher Andersen , journalist and author	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	Till 2014 , the NMMC was headquartered in an eight storied building in CBD Belapur .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Represented Indigenous All-Stars ( 2009 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Southend United F.C .	False
B_ORG O O O O O O O O	Episodes '' , 2011 ( writer / producer )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	1992 Major League Baseball expansion draft	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Crystal Snow Jenne	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Siliștea River ( Țibrin )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	Happy]] '' – Pharrell Williams	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Premier ( Canada )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Patterson Township , Beaver County , Pennsylvania	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Vinod Khanna , Shabana Azmi	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Benjamin N. Cardozo	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Communes of the Aude department	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Jonathan Thomas , 3 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Cark and Cartmel railway station	False
O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	*Written by Val Guest and Leslie Thomas	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Anurag Singh , 2012 / 13-2014 / 15	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	National Coalition Party 13.5 %	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG O	Beauvoir De Lisle , 1st Dragoons , commanded both the XIII and XV Corps .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Eastwood , Houston	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O	Jacqueline Novogratz is the founder and CEO of Acumen .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	`` Sign of the Times '' ( Bryan Ferry song ) , 1978	False
B_LOC O O O	Szczecin – 95.7 MHz	False
O O O O B_LOC O	It is found in Ecuador .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Billy Vessels ( RB ) en::	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Houston , Tennessee	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_ORG	Lake of Banyoles and S'Agaró	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Bugs Bunny , Yosemite Sam	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Buxton & Leek College	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	** Maués marmoset , ''Mico mauesi ''	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	'' The World at Large '' – en:4:32	False
O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	*Assemblyman Bob Andrzejczak ( D ) , and	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Seidou Njimoluh Njoya	False
O O O O B_LOC O	It is headquartered in Raleigh .	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	May 10 – Shel Silverstein , 68 , children 's poet	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER	en:: PG 87a-87b en:: Procopius of Gaza	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	State Senate District 39	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Miyazaki Athletic Stadium	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	en:: '' Atomic Dog '' by George Clinton	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	They currently reside in Lexington , Massachusetts .	False
O O B_PER I_PER	en:1:46.7 – Edward Burns	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	C & D Canal Museum	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Alexander Grant ( Massachusetts politician ) ( 1853– ?	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Emerson Aparecido Vivas Vergílio	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	South Los Angeles	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Burmese–Siamese War ( 1759–60 )	False
B_ORG O O O	Dance4life event 2006 .	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	'' 'Megahertz '' ' from Mighty Med ''	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	' '' The Green Monkey '' '	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER O	`` Elégie '' ( Jules Massenet )	False
O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	He came to Rossland , British Columbia in 1898 .	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	All degrees ( whether traditional on-campus , or distance ) are recognized by the New England Association of Schools and Colleges and the State of Connecticut ; .	False
O O B_LOC O O	' '' Ifni '' '	False
B_LOC O B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Oslo – Ullevaal Stadion ( 25,572 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Tommy Aaron ( 1 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Sam Lowes '' '	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	The Malwa Subah existed from 1568 to 1743 .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	San Cristóbal de La Laguna , España	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	University of Massachusetts Boston	False
O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER O O O O O	The song contains samples from `` Try Again '' by Aaliyah , `` Breathe and Stop '' by Q-Tip , and `` N.T .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Holy Trinity Church , Blythburgh	False
O B_ORG O O O O O B_PER I_PER	'' Pick-Up '' ( 1933 ) with Sylvia Sidney	False
O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	en:: Hans N. Andersen ( 11 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Kevin Johnson ( 9 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Riccardo Patrese '' '	False
O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O	The founder Mustafa Kemal Atatürk died .	False
O O O O B_ORG O O O	He was TV-host for Parlamentet in 2011 .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O	' '' James Auckland '' ' ' '' Travis Rettenmaier '' '7–5 , 6–7 ( 6 ) , [10–4]	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O O O O	' '' 7th US Army HQ , Heidelberg '' ' , FRG	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He was born in Upton , Massachusetts and died in Worcester , Massachusetts .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Jesús Rubio Martín	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Amanda Magarian / Jered Guzman	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	He is buried in Père Lachaise Cemetery .	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER O B_ORG I_ORG	Sivaji Ganesan , Sripriya , V.K. Ramasamy	False
O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	Both his parents were members of the Plymouth Brethren .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O	Bourke-White , Margaret .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Marquis de Condorcet	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER	*12 August 1681 en:: Charles Bertie	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O	Chita Rivera played the role of `` The Leader '' .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Cate Blanchett '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Free Software Foundation Europe	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Way of the Blade '' ( 2006 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O	**Monarch – Emperor Go-Daigo ( 1318–1339 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Bhagwan Mahaveer Sanctuary and Mollem National Park	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	NBA Rookie of the Year en:: 2007	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	A modern Twist ( ride ) .	False
O B_PER I_PER O O O	1–1 Rodrigo Taddei ( 54 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Double Bayou , Texas	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG O O	The album was a commercial success and sold almost eight million copies , according to Billboard '' .	False
B_LOC O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Jaipur ( Palace of the Winds )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Norte Region , Portugal	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	Digitised copy from Internet Archive .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Port of Spain , Trinidad and Tobago	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O	( 82.07 ) ' '' Colin Osborne '' '	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' Women 's 10,000 metres '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	New Forest Wildlife Park - Hampshire	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER	— Arranging lessons from Willie Maiden	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Henry I of Werle	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Venice Canal Historic District	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Richard Hanson Weightman	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER	All tracks written by Ray Davies	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	`` California Gurls '' - Katy Perry	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Brian O'Driscoll ( capt .	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	Victory shared with Eugen Bönsch	False
O O O B_LOC O B_ORG	19 , , Stockholm , Cirkus	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Waverly School District ( disambiguation )	False
O O O O B_LOC O	It is found in Europe .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lone Tree , Iowa	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	'' Metanarsia guberlica '' Nupponen , 2010	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Dwyane Wade ( 39 )	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	2004 en:: Real Gone Tour ''	False
O O B_PER I_PER O	Replaced by Robbie Groff .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Interstate 88 ( Illinois )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Isle of Man Railway stations	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	632 , Air Force Office of Special Investigations	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` Gin and Juice ''	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O	There is some intimation that Father Set may be one of the Great Old Ones that H. P. Lovecraft created .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O	' '' Dušan Lajović '' ' 7–6 ( 7–5 ) , 7–6 ( 7–5 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Vandré Sagrilo Monteiro	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	San Cristóbal de La Laguna	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Siah Piran-e Kasmai	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O	before 1870 and the Third Republic or	False
B_PER I_PER O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Owl Eyes – `` Pumped Up Kicks '' ( Foster the People )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	K ( Eighth Avenue Local )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	List of B-52 Units of the United States Air Force	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O O O	** High Explosive ( HE )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O O	His son , John V , cosied up to Guaimar IV of Salerno and eventually did homage to him .	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	( ** Represents NFL Combine )	False
B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER	Francisco Clavet Marcelo Ríos Takao Suzuki Sjeng Schalken	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	Head coach en:: Todor Veselinović	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Council of Churches of Malaysia	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	'' The Partridge Family ''	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER	File en:: J150W-Ayers.jpg |Sir Henry Ayers	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Pedro Téllez-Girón , 1st Duke of Osuna	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	BP Ford Abu Dhabi World Rally Team	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	Common ringed plover , ''Charadrius hiaticula ''	False
B_LOC O B_LOC O	Villefranche near Nice .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	`` Love Needs No Disguise ''	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Mang Thít District	False
O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	( See article en:: Entropy ( statistical views ) ) .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O	Lancelot Strong , the Shield '' 1-2 ( 1983 )	False
O O O B_ORG O	''Look Out , Houndour !	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Midnight at Minton 's '' ( 1941 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Legal systems of the world	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	This was the first production that Charlie Chaplin came to .	False
B_PER I_PER O O	Milt Pappas , 2012	False
O O O B_LOC O	He died in Romillé .	False
O O O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O O O	The ports of Cádiz , La Spezia , Naples and Toulon were visited .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Geneva II Conference on Syria	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Stoke Bridge , Ipswich	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Teniorhinus niger '' ( Druce , 1910 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O	Aloha Bowl en:: 22 Michigan State 33 , 23 13	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Scoparia niphospora '' ( Meyrick , 1884 )	False
O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O	*1973 ''North Face '' , Wetterhorn Peak , San Juan Mountains , Colorado .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O O O O	Pic du Midi de Bigorre , France ( ''ETs '' )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Arnold , Nebraska – $ 18,574	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	West Melbourne , Victoria	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O	'' Mythimna impura '' ( Hübner , 1808 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Nicolaus Olahus ( 1543 - 1548 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Roy Stewart as Nosha ( uncredited )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Palau Municipal d'Esports de Badalona	False
B_LOC O O O O	Glenwood ( vast majority )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Imperial College Business School	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	53 feet ( 16 m ) - Squaw Island Light , Michigan	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	José Luís Ábalos Meco	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	U.S. Route 211	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O O O O O	She was reportedly set against moving from St Albans , Hertfordshire to York , North Yorkshire , resulting in her husband turning down the offer .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	List of works by Auguste Carli	False
O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG O B_LOC O	In September 2011 , he signed a one-year contract with PAOK in Greece .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Six Celan Songs • The Ballad of Kastriot Rexhepi	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	E.A. Diddle Arena , Bowling Green , Kentucky	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	1968–69 Honduran Liga Nacional	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Drums and Guns	False
B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O O O	Pat Garrity , George McCloud ( 15 )	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	He started by beating Iván Navarro in straight sets and eventually lost to 12th ranked David Ferrer .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Aspropotamos , Trikala	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O B_LOC O O O	In 1606 and 1607 the Plymouth Company sent ships into the area to colonize , but the settlers of the Popham Colony and those who settled along the Kennebec River returned to England in 1608 .	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O	' '' King Edward Point '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	The Power Team ( TV series )	False
B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER	Barbara Schett Amanda Coetzer Jana Novotná Lindsay Davenport	False
B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Bad Schwartau , Schleswig-Holstein	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	** '' Kingdom of Pamplona '' ' - García Sánchez II ( 994–1004 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Dwight Howard ( 12 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	' '' Chris Short '' ' ( 6–7 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Olli Tuominen '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Lalit Mohan Sharma , former Chief Justice of India	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	A Dramatic Turn of Events '' ( 2011 )	False
O O O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	''Lawe '' left the Gulf of Tonkin on 14 May .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	North Frontenac , Ontario	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Red Raw & Sore ''	False
O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O O	** Aljunied GRC , Ang Mo Kio GRC , Cheng San GRC , Hong Kah GRC were increased from four -member GRCs to five-member GRCs .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Ian Woosnam ( 2 )	False
O O O O B_LOC O B_LOC O	It is found in Bolivia and Peru .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Colegio de la Preciosa Sangre de Pichilemu	False
O O O O O B_PER I_PER O B_LOC O O O O O O O O O O O O O	'' 'QB '' ' - AJ McCarron , Alabama ( ' '' AFCA '' ' , ' '' WCFF '' ' )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O	Tebeau , Charlton W .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Okolona , Arkansas – $ 14,318	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O O	Hip Hop and the World We Live In '' ( 2002 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' Scott Pruett '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	Berliner FC Dynamo ( 6 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Dar Gol-e Seyyed Hasan	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Captain Miša 's Mansion	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O	In 2001 he was elected the Rector of the University of Dundee .	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O	Deputy-mayor of Massy , Essonne , 1983–1995 .	False
B_LOC O B_LOC O O O O	Galway , Ireland ( since 1987 )	False
O O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER O B_PER I_PER	Tries en:: Todd Carney , Ricky Leutele , Michael Gordon , Jeff Robson	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Galapagos snake eel	False
O O O O B_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O O O O	The album 's lead single , titled `` Bounce with Me '' was released on August 8 , 2000 .	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG O	*** Mountain Standard Time ( UTC-07 ) , Mountain Daylight Time ( UTC-06 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Philip Glass ( 1937- )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	White Mountain National Forest	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Vilar do Paraíso	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Stapleton Cotton , 1st Viscount Combermere	False
O O O O O O O B_LOC O	Before 1945 the area was part of Germany .	False
O O B_PER I_PER O O	' '' John Eckstein '' '	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER O	Zaal'Koris is voiced by Martin Jarvis .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Peter Sandhu5,446 ( 39.58 % )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O B_PER I_PER	`` Ca n't Get You Out of My Head '' by Kylie Minogue	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O O O	Celtic Park , Glasgow ( 60,832 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Giovanni Battista Riccioli	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC O	In October 1890 , uncertain of his destination , he boarded the Union Pacific Railroad in Omaha .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	Joe Perry ( June 6 , 1992 )	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	She has received honorary degrees from the University of Utah , Weber State University , Salt Lake Community College , and the College of Eastern Utah .	False
B_LOC I_LOC O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Davao City - General Santos City	False
B_LOC O O B_LOC O	Larissos ( near Araxos )	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	She also used some handcrafted techniques which she displayed at the 1935 Brussels International Exhibition .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O	François Le Lionnais ( October 3 , 1901 – March 13 , 1984 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O	William Eggleston ( born 1939 ) , photographer	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Bannered routes of U.S. Route 6	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Punta del Este / Montevideo	False
O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O B_LOC	'' Canal des houillères de la Sarre '' in Gondrexange	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	CONCACAF U-17 Championship	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Walter B. Woodbury	False
B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER I_PER	Scott Sharp Johannes van Overbeek	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_LOC O	Roadway flooding along U.S. Route 130 was reported in Collingswood .	False
O O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O	The first recipient was his replacement , George Hainsworth .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Croy , Highland and Dalcross , Highland	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Communist Party of Nepal ( UML )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O B_LOC O	Defending titlist is Kaisa Mäkäräinen of Finland .	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG O B_LOC O B_LOC O	' '' Gisselberg '' ' is a Stadtteil of Marburg in Hesse .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Luis de Morales	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O O B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O	The main opposition parties of Fine Gael and the Labour Party were also in favour .	False
O O O B_PER I_PER	24 Apr – Heinrich Himmler	False
O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	File en:: Lhasatrainstation Lhasa Railway Station	False
O O O O O O B_ORG O O O O	He appeared in an episode of Gibbsville '' in 1976 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O	30 June - Opening of the Prichard Jones Institute at Newborough , Anglesey .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Medfra , Alaska	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC	Bermudian Springs High School , York Springs	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Reichenau , Switzerland	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	Juan de Araujo ( 1646–1712 )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Outline of the creation–evolution controversy	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	LaGrange , New York	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Ray ( wrestler )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Henry II the Pious	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Natchez , Mississippi	False
O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	' '' Daytime Emmy Awards '' '	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_LOC	Maha Sarakham University , Thailand	False
O O O O B_PER I_PER O	Thunderon is voiced by Alonzo Bodden .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Hissar ( disambiguation )	False
O O B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O	** '' Duchy of Gaeta '' ' - John I , Hypatus of Gaeta ( 906–933 )	False
B_ORG O O O	Putties ( a.k.a .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Shazia Sikander ( M.F.A .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Communes of the Somme department	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O	Joe Presko , P , 1957–1958	False
O O B_PER O O	' '' Deadmau5 '' '	False
O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG O	It is found on the Galapagos Islands .	False
O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O O O O O	He served as Chief Justice of India from 1943 to 1947 .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O	Nick Slyney , 12 .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O	JGC Corporation ( )	False
O O O O O O B_LOC I_LOC O O B_PER I_PER O	He was named to the second-team Big East along with Tyvon Branch .	False
O O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O	Two tramcars survive , both in the National Tramway Museum collection .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	Reed Between the Lines ''	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O	Prince of Lies '' , by James Lowder ( paperback , August 1993 , ISBN 978-1-56076-626-1 ; paperback re-issue , September 2003 , ISBN 978-0-7869-3114-9 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Charles I , Duke of Brunswick-Wolfenbüttel	False
O O O B_LOC O	en:: en:: en:: A. ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	M. B. W. Tent	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_PER I_PER O O	Solicitor General for England and Wales – Harriet Harman – 2001	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_PER I_PER	Premier of Newfoundland - Clyde Wells	False
B_PER I_PER O O	Tom Corcoran , author	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	** European Astronaut Centre ( ''EAC '' ) of the European Space Agency ;	False
B_PER I_PER O O	John Parr , producer	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Interchange ( road )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Royal Hospital for Sick Children - University of Glasgow	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O	• Donja Nevlja ( 31 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Sultan of Johor en:: Sultan Ibrahim Ismail	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Abbey of Our Lady of Gethsemani	False
O B_LOC O O O	• Smoljinac ( 1873 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	National Gallery of Australia	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O	Deportivo Pereira ( 1 )	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Strikeforce en:: Feijao vs. Henderson	False
O O O O O O B_ORG O O O O O O	The case is steeply conical and headspaces on the conical case walls .	False
O O B_ORG O O	' '' Related '' '	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Graeme Le Saux	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Aldeburgh ( UK Parliament constituency )	False
O O O B_PER I_PER O O O O O	*Released as a Mick Jagger solo single in November 1970	False
O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B_ORG O	There are currently 76 vehicles available to members , with the majority of them located in Kitchener-Waterloo .	False
B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG	FedEx Express operates Boeing 767-300F and Airbus A300-600	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Tracks ( Bruce Springsteen album )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Griffin ( Dan Vado )	False
O B_LOC I_LOC O O O B_PER I_PER I_PER O O O	'' Byzantine Empire '' ' - John V Palaiologos ( 1341–1391 )	False
B_ORG O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O B_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC O O O O O O	Indianapolis , Kansas City , Portland , St. Louis and Hartford are tied with three each .	False
B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	Army of the Potomac	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	** Lars Frederiksen and the Bastards – Lars Frederiksen and the Bastards ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Eileen M. Rehrmann	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O O O	Chicago Bulls ( waived on December 16 )	False
O O O O O O B_PER I_PER O O O	He was defeated for re-election by Travis Tranel in 2010 .	False
B_PER I_PER O O	Elizabeth Charleston , painter	False
B_LOC O O O O O	Ctenopharynx '' ( 3 species )	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O O O O	`` Dead By X-Mas '' ( 1981 )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	P. J. Nolan	False
O B_PER I_PER I_PER	en:: Marcus Tulio Tanaka	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER O	Kubrat , Prince of Panagyurishte .	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER I_PER	Charismatic Episcopal Church bishops	False
O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG I_ORG	** United States Post Office ( Jackson Heights , Queens )	False
O O O B_ORG O	He was a Democrat .	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O	Kyle Farnsworth came on and got the third out , but the damage was done .	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC O B_LOC	Sydney Cricket Ground , Sydney	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Laz River ( Someș )	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Joseph L. Doob	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Wemindji , Quebec	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O O O	Kate Sullivan - anchor / reporter ( 2000–2006 )	False
B_LOC O B_LOC O O O	Cap-d'Ail , France ( H )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Pine Grove , Amador County , California	False
O B_LOC O B_LOC O O	en:: Zvolen , Slovakia - 2007	False
B_PER I_PER B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Ekaterina Makarova Bruno Soares ( 1 / 3 )	False
B_PER I_PER O O O O O	Ketevan Orbeliani ( according to tradition )	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Papua New Guinea	False
O O B_ORG O O	' '' Skindred '' '	False
B_LOC I_LOC I_LOC	Lago di Bilancino	False
O B_ORG O B_ORG I_ORG I_ORG O	; *NSYNC – No Strings Attached ''	False
B_PER I_PER I_PER	Calcium channel blocker	False
B_ORG I_ORG O O O O	Common whimbrel , ''Numenius phaeopus ''	False
O B_LOC O B_LOC O	Within Gujarat , India ,	False
